<?xml version="1.0"?>
<web-site>
    <page id="index" name="Home">
        <title>Welcome</title>
        <content>
            <p>
                Welcome to the 11<sup>th</sup> Bournemouth Scout Group.
            </p>
            <p>
                This web-site is under development. We're hoping
                to add more information in the next few weeks.
            </p>
            <p>
                The Scout Association provides adventurous activities and personal development opportunities for 400,000 young people
                aged 6-25. Internationally, we have over 28 million young people enjoying the benefits of Scouting
                across 218 countries. Personal development means promoting the physical, intellectual, social and
                spiritual well-being of the individual, helping them achieve their full potential. In Scouting, we
                believe that young people develop most when they are 'learning by doing,' when they are given
                responsibility, work in teams, take acceptable risks and think for themselves.
            </p>
            <p>
                Please contact the Group Scout Leader by e-mail at
                <a href="mailto:bournemouth11th@hotmail.co.uk">bournemouth11th@hotmail.co.uk</a>
                for information.
            </p>
        </content>
    </page>
    <page id="beavers" name="Beavers">
        <title>Beaver Scouts</title>
        <content>
            <p>
                Beaver Scouts are the youngest section of the Scouting family. 
                Their activities are based around: making things, outdoor activities, singing, playing games, 
                going out on visits, investigating nature, listening to stories, learning how to be safe and 
                most importantly, making new friends.
            </p>
            <p>
                Children join a Beaver Scout Colony for many reasons. It might be they have heard great things from
                their friends about all the things the Colony gets up to every week.
            </p>
            <p>
                There are a lot of Beavers at 11<sup>th</sup> Bournemouth, just waiting for you to jump in and join them! 
            </p>
        </content>
        <page id="beavers-leaders" name="Beaver Leaders">
            <title>Beaver Leaders</title>
            <content>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Beaver Scout Leaders:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Lou Branch (Robin)</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Jay Branch (King Louie)</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Regular Beaver Helpers:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Rea</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Zoe</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </content>
        </page>
    </page>
    <page id="cubs" name="Cubs">
        <title>Cub Scouts</title>
        <content>
            <p>
                Cubs, or Cub Scouts are boys and girls between the ages of 8 years and 10½ years.
                They are divided into small groups called "Sixes". Each Six is led by a Sixer with help from a 
                Seconder. Some packs have a Senior Sixer, usually the oldest Cub just preparing to join Scouts. 
            </p>
            <h3>Awards</h3>
            <p>
                You probably know that Cubs earn badges. These are usually red, with a yellow border and circular.
                These can be for a whole range of subjects from Animal Lover to Writer and from Computer to 
                World Conservationist. There are also Challenge badges to be earned. These include Outdoor Challenge 
                and Fitness Challenge.
            </p>
            <p>
                The highest award is the Chief Scout's Silver Award.                
            </p>
            <h3>Activities</h3>
            <p>
                Cubs enjoy adventurous activities. The Cubs are able to try out many adventurous activities such as 
                Abseiling, Air Rifle Shooting, Archery and Canoeing, as well as going Camping and Hiking.
                All activites are supervised by National Governing Body qualified instructors, many of whom are 
                Scouters themselves. 
            </p>
            <p>
                Cubs also go on outings, to Marwell Zoo and Legoland for example.
            </p>
        </content>
        <page id="cubs-leaders" name="Cub Leaders">
            <title>Cub Leaders</title>
            <content>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Cub Scout Leaders:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Louise Peake (Akela)</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Assistant Cub Scout Leaders:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Lisa Poulson (Baloo)</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Gary Faulkner (Kaa)</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </content>
        </page>
    </page>
    <page id="scouts" name="Scouts">
        <title>Welcome to Scouts</title>
        <content>
            <p>
                A Scout is aged between 10½ and 14 years. Scouts are young people who want to make friends and
                develop widening interests in ways that are both educational and fun. 
                Scouting is perfect if you want a break from the usual after-school routine of homework, 
                games and watching television.
            </p>
            <h3>Uniform</h3>
            <p>
                Scouts wear the new teal green smart shirt, a pair of navy blue activity trousers and their 
                Group scarf (see right). A Cub joining the Scout Section, who has gained his or her Silver Chief Scout Award, 
                may wear that award on his or her uniform until he or she gains the Gold Chief Scout Award. 
                He or she may also wear his or her Participation and Moving On awards.
            </p>
            <h3>Activities</h3>
            <p>
                Scout activities are about action and involvement and this means more than just camping.
            </p>
            <p>
                Hiking, rock climbing, gliding, sailing, pioneering, canoeing, parascending, abseiling, putting
                on shows and exhibitions, motor mechanics, electronics, photography - the list is endless! 
                Scouts are also given the chance to learn skills in survival, cooking and first aid. 
            </p>
            <p>
                There are often opportunities to go abroad.
            </p>
            <p>
                
            </p>
            <p>
                
            </p>
        </content>
        <page id="scout-leaders" name="Scout Leaders">
            <title>Scout Leaders</title>
            <content>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Scout Leader:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Jeremy Edwards</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Assistant Scout Leaders:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Jack Edwards</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Beth Davies</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <table style="margin:20px 0px; text-align:left">
                    <tr>
                        <th>Assistant Cub Scout Leader:</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:5px 20px">Lisa Poulson</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </content>
        </page>
    </page>
    <page id="contact" name="Contact Us">
        <title>Contact Details</title>
        <content>
            <p>
                Please contact the Group Scout Leader by e-mail at
                <a href="mailto:bournemouth11th@hotmail.co.uk">bournemouth11th@hotmail.co.uk</a>
                for information.
            </p>
        </content>
    </page>
</web-site>
